(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-20T02:03:53.540873",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドライブ
Welcome to L-challenger, everyone attending
L-challengerにお越しの皆さん！
Takane Lui's Birthday Band Live!
待たせたね！
Thanks for waiting!
ホロックスの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します！
I'm Takane Lui, executive officer of Secret Society holoX!
本日は待ちに待った生誕ライブ！
Today is the long-awaited Birthday Live!
開演に先立ちまして、注意事項とお知らせです！
Before we begin, here are some notices and announcements!
このライブは全編無料、生バンドでお送りいたします！
This entire live stream is completely free with a live band!
絶対に見逃せない超超超超重大発表もございますので
We also have a super super super super major announcement you can't miss,
最後までぜひ見ていってくださいね！
so please stay tuned until the very end!
感想はハッシュタグ「鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドライブ」になっております！
Use the hashtag #TakaneLuiBirthdayBandLive to share your thoughts!
SNSでスクショ付きでガンガンポストして盛り上がってくれると嬉しいです！
I'd love it if you post lots of screenshots on social media to build hype!
そして本編終了後の21時15分からは
And starting at 21:15 after the main stream ends,
メンバーシップ限定ライブもございます！
there will also be a membership-exclusive live concert!
メンバーシップライブももちろん生バンドで歌っちゃいますので
Of course, I'll be singing with a live band during the membership stream too,
この機会にメンバーシップへのご参加、お待ちしております！
so I look forward to you joining membership on this occasion!
さて、ここからはお知らせです！
Now then, onto the announcements!
早く集まってくださった皆さんに
For everyone who arrived early,
鷹嶺ルイ誕生日記念2024グッズ情報を先出ししたいと思います！
I'd like to give a sneak peek at the Takane Lui Birthday 2024 merch!
今回のグッズは4種類！
There are 4 merch items in total this time!
最初はこちら！
First up is this!
ライブと言えばビッグタオル！
Speaking of live shows, a big towel!
今回のライブテーマにぴったりな、かっこよく歌う私を、かかげパパが描き下ろしてくれました！ありがとう！
Kakage-papa drew a cool illustration of me singing that fits this live's theme! Thank you!
大きなタオルなので、イベントで背中からかければ、ルイ推しをアピールできちゃいます！
Since it's a huge towel, wearing it over your shoulders at events shows you're a Lui fan!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ランダム缶バッジ！楽器を演奏する可愛いイラストが全4種類！
Random pin badges! Featuring cute illustrations playing instruments, 4 designs in total!
1種類がランダムで封入されております！
Each pack contains one random design!
イラストはGurin.先生に描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！
The artwork was drawn by Gurin.-sensei! Thank you so much!
これはね、すっごい可愛いので、全種類集めたくなっちゃいますよね！
These are super cute, so you'll definitely want to collect all of them!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
おでかけルイぬいぐるみ！
Going-Out Lui Plushie!
先日お披露目されたばかりの新衣装がぬいぐるみになって登場です！
My new outfit that was just unveiled recently is now available as a plushie!
かなりリクエストが多かった、持ち運びしやすいサイズ...
It's a highly requested portable size...
になっておりますので
So...
いろんなところに連れて行っていただければなと思います
...I hope you'll take it with you to many places!
最後はこちら
Last up is this!
ボディ痛バ！
Body Ita Bag!
今回のランダム缶バッジやおでかけぬいぐるみとの相性もバッチリの痛バッグが登場です！
An ita bag that goes perfectly with the random badges and plushie has arrived!
私のモチーフがさりげなくあしらわれたデザインで、男女問わず使えるバッグになっております
Featuring a subtle motif of mine, it's designed for anyone to use regardless of gender!
ストラップ位置を変えることでショルダーバッグにもなる2WAY仕様です
By changing the strap position, it turns into a shoulder bag—a 2-way design!
ぜひこれを持ってルイ推しを全力アピールしてください！
Please carry this and show off your support for Lui with all your heart!
と言ったことでこちらの4種類のグッズが全て入ったフルセットもご用意しております
So, we also have a Full Set containing all 4 of these merch items!
フルセットには箔押し複製サイン入りチケット風特典カードと特典ボイスがついております
The Full Set includes a foil-stamped replica signed ticket card and a bonus voice!
今回直筆特典は数量限定バージョンでご用意させていただきました
The handwritten bonus is available in a limited quantity version!
今回はですね、直筆メッセージを心を込めて入れさせていただきます
I'll be writing handwritten messages with all my heart!
数量限定ですが、いつもより多めに用意させていただきましたので、一人でも多くの方に手に取ってもらえたら嬉しいです！
Although limited, I prepared more than usual, so I hope as many people as possible can get one!
特典ボイスはライブの後の打ち上げパーティーをイメージしたシチュエーションボイスになっております
The bonus voice is a situation voice themed after an after-concert celebration party!
今回も私が台本を書かせていただきました！
I wrote the script for it again this time!
こちらは通常も限定バージョンにも共通で入ってくる特典になっておりますので、ぜひ聴いていただけると嬉しいです！
This bonus comes with both the regular and limited versions, so please give it a listen!
グッズはこのライブ本編終了後の21時からホロライブプロダクションのオフィシャルショップで販売開始になります！
Merch sales start at 21:00 after this concert on the Hololive Production Official Shop!
ライブを楽しんだ後はグッズもよろしくね！
After enjoying the concert, please check out the merch too!
お待たせしました！
Thank you for waiting!
鷹嶺ルイ 生誕バンドLIVE「L-challenger」まもなく開演です！
Takane Lui Birthday Band LIVE "L-challenger" is about to begin!
この日のためにたくさん準備をしてきました！
I've prepared so much for this day!
全力で歌うので最後までみんなで盛り上がっていきましょう！
I'll sing with all my heart, so let's get hyped together until the very end!
準備はいいかー！
Are you ready?!
それでは行きましょう！まずはオープニングアクトです！
Here we go! First up is the opening act!
ボルテージを上げてくれるユニットといえば？
Who's the unit that'll kick the hype into overdrive?
La La PaTa Pa La Na PaTa...
迷宮なラビリンス
Labyrinth of a Maze
のうのう招かれた SHOW TIME 場
Carefreely invited to the Showtime stage
秘密一秘の秘匿 MANSION
Secret hidden mansion
ガタガタのドアの向こうに
Beyond the rattling doors
NO PAIN NO GAIN A B C
狙ううまそうな COOK EYE
Targeting a delicious-looking cook eye
迫るホグワホグワイ
Approaching hogwahogwai
放射状にとった構図はどうだろう？
How about a radial composition?
エゴイスティックに奪われていくよ
Egoistically being taken away
かっこいいでござる！
So cool, de gozaru!
通常なき解脱痛感
Unordinary realization of liberation
ドアからドアへリュウチョウ
Fluently moving door to door
咲かす愚夜より妙はに響け
Echoing strangely beyond a foolish night
笑い声
Laughter
La La PaTa Pa La Na PaTa...
つまり本気！
Meaning we're serious!
思考のストッパー！
Thought stopper!
ステキな迷宮のラビリンス！
A wonderful labyrinth of a maze!
並び立つシルエット
Silhouettes standing side-by-side
超不評で切断 Wi-Fi
Disconnected Wi-Fi due to bad reviews
これマジで最強ルーティン探検隊
This is truly the ultimate routine expedition team
館内の回廊は本当に
The corridors in the mansion are really...
危ないって MANSION...
...dangerous in this mansion...
ワンキー！ 虚実！
One key! Truth and falsehood!
虚実踊るマリオネット
Marionette dancing between truth and falsehood
こちらへは何度目だ？
How many times have you been here?
ランク外は眼中ないがなんくらいあかんくない？
Unranked isn't on my radar, but isn't that pretty bad?
エゴイスティックに捕り込まれてくくく
Egoistically drawn in, kekeke
迷える子羊くんたちー！
Wandering little lambs~!
お砂糖、マヨネーズ、それとピンクのナマモノいっぱいでハイになれるドリンクできたよー！
I made a drink with sugar, mayo, and lots of pink creatures to get you high~!
ロックで飲んでくださいね！ホロックスだけに！ハッハー！
Drink it on the rocks! 'Cause we're holoX! Ha-ha!
流石、皆様の女房でござる！
As expected of everyone's wife, de gozaru!
お、意外といけるのー！
Oh, it's surprisingly good!
いやお前が飲むんかい！
Wait, you're the one drinking it?!
じゃ、とりあえず... 乾杯！
Well then, for now... Cheers!
You are my special
鏡の回廊から
From the mirror corridor,
天意を反証せよ
disprove the divine will.
塗り替えられる勝負(ジャッジ)や
Matches that can be rewritten,
見外せろ
look away from them.
笑い声 お前たちもな
Laughter, you guys as well.
パララパタ パララパタ ラララパタ パララパタ エッ
Pa-ra-ra-pa-ta, pa-ra-ra-pa-ta, ra-ra-ra-pa-ta, pa-ra-ra-pa-ta, eh!
パララパタ パパラララパタ ラララパタ パララプタ パララパタ
Pa-ra-ra-pa-ta, pa-pa-ra-ra-ra-pa-ta, ra-ra-ra-pa-ta, pa-ra-ru-pu-ta, pa-ra-pa-ta!
さあ集え 孤高の元
Now gather under solitude,
肩組んで 声を高らかに
arm in arm, raise your voices high.
パララパタ ラララパタ エッ
Pa-ra-ra-pa-ta, ra-ra-ra-pa-ta, eh!
エデンの海を越えるため
To cross the sea of Eden,
つまり本気
in short, we're serious.
苦痛が痛い
Pain hurts!
敵無き 迷宮のスーパーフューチャーパーティーラビリンス
An unrivaled labyrinth super future party labyrinth!
We are HoloX!
猫又おかゆ
[Nekomata Okayu]
森カリオペ
[Mori Calliope]
宝鐘マリン
[Houshou Marine]
常闇トワ
[Tokoyami Towa]
ラプラス・ダークネス
[La+ Darknesss]
白衣こより
[Hakui Koyori]
沙花叉クロヱ
[Sakamata Chloe]
風真いろは
[Kazama Iroha]
鷹嶺ルイ
[Takane Lui]
Welcome, Lui's Birthday Party!
Welcome to Lui's Birthday Party!
今日は楽しんでいこう！
Let's have fun today!
生バンドです！
It's a live band!
1曲目はオリジナル曲！
The first song is an original song!
新しいオリジナル曲です！「Tori To Re:TreaT」聴いてください！
It's a new original song! Please listen to "Tori To Re:TreaT"!
喧騒に紛れ君参上
Amidst the noise, you make your entrance.
掻き分けて私の世界
Pushing through into my world.
開幕すでに無限理想郷(ユートピア)で
The curtain rises already on an infinite utopia,
既に君は僕の虜
and you are already my captive.
T-T-T-Treat T-T-T-Treat エデンはそこに
T-T-T-Treat, T-T-T-Treat... Eden is right there.
爪を隠して
Hiding my claws,
誘ってみせる
I'll entice you.
類は友を呼ぶ
Birds of a feather flock together.
Welcome to my retreat!
ワン・ツー・スリー Treat! Treat! Treat!
One, two, three, Treat! Treat! Treat!
ようこそ取り巻いて
Welcome, gather around me,
世界をトリコにしてみせて
and captivate the entire world!
Treat! Treat! Treat!
鳥一途にご注意
Beware of my single-minded bird nature,
高所へいざなうの
inviting you to high places.
毎度様 私の世界へ
Welcome as always to my world.
道標の神罰
Divine punishment serving as a guide,
最後に華咲かせて
making flowers bloom at the very end.
Treat!
鳥条にのっとりガーデン
A garden governed by bird rules,
あいまいに日曜日 ルイラーの家はどうも
vaguely on Sunday, welcome to the Luira home!
揺れる過去の Pendulum
The swinging pendulum of the past
鵜の目鷹の目が回る
Prying eyes spin around
暗雲低迷 絶体絶命
Dark clouds hang low, in a desperate pitch
君は過去の虜
You are a prisoner of the past
歪な秘密
A warped secret
話してあげる
I'll tell you about it
飛ぶ鳥を落として
Striking down birds in flight
Welcome to my little territory
Treat, treat, treat! ようこそ鳥籠へ
Treat, treat, treat! Welcome to the birdcage
世界はトリコで満ちていく
The world fills up with captives
Treat, treat, treat! 好奇心にご用心
Treat, treat, treat! Beware of your curiosity
振り出しの Welcome, my world
Back to square one, welcome to my world
Treat, treat, treat! ようこそ鳥籠へ
Treat, treat, treat! Welcome to the birdcage
世界はトリコで満たして
Fill the world with captives
Treat, treat, treat! ありえないほど愛を
Treat, treat, treat! With an unbelievable amount of love
揺らして Welcome, 私の世界へ
Shake it up, welcome to my world
的外れ 危険ダンス 嫉妬心も重ねて 放て
Off-target, dangerous dance, stack up envy and fire away
猟奇的 嘘つきの 逃避行の果てまで
Bizarre and deceitful, to the end of the getaway
世界をずっとトリコにするから この歌のラスト飾るの
I'll captivate the world forever, crowning the end of this song
続いては...
Up next...
カリを呼びたいと思います！
I'd like to call Calli on stage!
Hey, hey, everybody! What's up?!
一緒に歌いましょう！
Let's sing together!
Let's rock!
もう意地になっちゃって 格好つけて 格好良くない
Getting stubborn and putting on airs, it's not cool at all
そういうの嫌になってんだ ほっといてよ 知りたくない
I'm sick of that stuff, leave me alone, I don't wanna know
もう被害者ぶっちゃってさ 嫉妬したり じっと出来ない
Playing the victim, jealous and unable to sit still,
聞こえないように愚痴さえだって 言ってくりゃあ しんどいな
bitching out of earshot, it's exhausting.
僕の事誰も覗かないよ
Nobody ever peers into my life,
だから僕のことそっとしといて
so just leave me alone.
うるさい！
Shut up!
だけど陰にハイハイハイ ウケる またのめり込んでいるね だとか
But in the shadows, yeah yeah yeah, hilarious, "You're getting sucked in again,"
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫
actually terrified, just a barking coward.
痛いくせに耐えてハイハイハイ いつも平気なふりばっかりなの 僕は
Hurt as you are, enduring it, yeah yeah yeah, always just pretending you're fine,
壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで ててて怖いジャン
I laugh behind my walls, don't come any closer, it's scary.
ばかばっか ばかばっか ばかばっか やだ ばかばっか
Fools all around, fools all around, fools all around, no way, fools all around.
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってんの？
Give it a rest, are you still mad?
ほっといてよ ほっとできない
Leave me alone! I can't leave you alone!
見ないように目を逸らしたって ついてくるじゃん やっぱり
Even if I look away, you still follow me around, of course.
こんな愚痴言わなきゃいいじゃん 隠さなくたっていいじゃん
You shouldn't complain like that! You don't have to hide it!
いやいやいやいやいやいやいや それが良くない
No no no no no no no, that's no good.
僕の事誰も覗かないよ
Nobody ever peers into my life,
だから僕のことそっとしといて
so just leave me alone.
そんなこと全部大丈夫だと 言えたらいいのにな
I wish I could say that everything is alright.
思えたらいいのにな
I wish I could really feel that way.
違うよ だからね 大正解! そう、僕はその通りなの
Wrong! So you see, spot on! Yes, I'm exactly like that.
また言いたい事殺すんだから もう忘れてくれ
Since I'm suppressing what I want to say again, just forget about me.
うわっはっはっは！
Bwahahaha!
痛いくせに耐えてハイハイハイ ウケる またのめり込んでいるね だとか
Hurt as you are, enduring it, yeah yeah yeah, hilarious, "You're getting sucked in again,"
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫
actually terrified, just a barking coward.
痛いくせに耐えてハイハイハイ いつも平気なふりばっかりなの 僕は
Hurt as you are, enduring it, yeah yeah yeah, always just pretending you're fine,
壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで どうか
I laugh behind my walls, don't come any closer, please.
本当バカだ いい加減バカ とんだバカばっか ダサいなって
Seriously an idiot, a real idiot, nothing but total fools, so uncool.
そんなこと言ったって僕もやっぱ どうしようもないんだわ
Even if you say that, I can't help it either.
点状感性の相違抱えて 痛い痛い死ねるって
Holding onto point-like differences in sensitivity, "It hurts so much I could die."
僕も口ばっかだね 今日も壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで ててて怖いジャン
I'm all talk too, today again I laugh behind my walls, don't come any closer, it's scary.
ばかばっか ほら ばかばっか
Fools all around, see, fools all around.
ということで、改めまして...
And so, once again...
ちょっと喉がやばい（笑）
My throat is kind of wrecked (laughs).
ああ、大丈夫？カリも...膝もやばい！
Ah, are you okay? Calli too... my knees are wrecked too!
大丈夫、大丈夫です！
I'm fine, we're fine!
ちょっと水飲んできていいですか？
Can I go grab a drink of water?
そうですね、降りたいと思う...
Yeah, I'd like to get a drink too...
じゃあ、カリ、自己紹介をしてて貰ってもいいですか？
Then Calli, could you do your self-introduction while I'm away?
オッケーです！任せて！
Okay! Leave it to me!
お願いします！
Please do!
あー！みなさん！
Ah! Everyone!
いつも頑張ってる死神、カリオペ・モーリ
It's the hard-working reaper, Calliope Mori,
ですよね！ホロライブEnglish -Myth-の
right! Hololive English -Myth-'s
死神弟子デス！破滅はここデスデス！
Reaper apprentice desu! Destruction is right here desu desu!
Hey, everyone! Thank you for watching!
いやあ、楽しい...ごめんごめんごめん！
Man, this is so fun... sorry, sorry, sorry!
ごめん、楽しすぎる！
Sorry, this is too much fun!
いや、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます！
Man, thank you so much for coming today!
いやいや、こちらこそ誘ってくれてありがとうございました！
No no, thank you for inviting me!
本当にね...
Seriously...
歌いたかったんで
I really wanted to sing it.
そうだね、すごい好きな曲。なんか、めちゃめちゃ緊張してた、実は。
Yeah, I love that song so much. Honestly, I was super nervous...
あら！でもめちゃカッコよかったです！
Oh, really? But you looked so cool!
そうだね、沸してなんか…バンドもいるよね！
Yeah! And also... there's a live band too!
そう！すごい！わぁ、本当にびっくりした！
Right! Amazing! Wow, I was really surprised!
生バンドでお送りしております！
We're bringing this to you with a live band!
カッコいい！めちゃめちゃカッコいい！
So cool! Really, really cool!
これからもちょっと生バンドでお送りしたいと思いますので
We'd like to continue performing with the live band, so...
#鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドLIVE でたくさん呟いてくださると嬉しいです！
We'd love it if you tweet a lot using #TakaneLuiBirthdayBandLIVE!
使って使って！
Please use it!
はい、今トレンド4位みたいなので
Yeah, apparently it's currently #4 on trending...
うわ！お！1位まで押し上げてくれ！
Whoa! Ooh! Push it all the way to #1!
お願いしまーす！
Please!
お願いしまーす！頑張ってみんな！お願い！
Please! Do your best, everyone! Pretty please!
ということで、カリが出てきたということは…
So, with Calli appearing here, that means...
ここから実はゲストパートになるので、収録もしてあるんですけれども
From here on is actually the guest section, which was pre-recorded,
バンドの…これもねバンドなんで、ぜひゲストパートをこれから3曲続けて見ていただければなと思います！
but with the band—since this is with a live band too, please enjoy the next 3 guest songs!
その間に喉を休めてきます！
In the meantime, I'm going to go rest my throat!
ということで、カリありがとう！
So, thank you so much, Calli!
いえいえ！こちらこそ楽しかった！
Not at all! I had a total blast too!
じゃあ一緒にパート振ってもらってもいいですか？
Then, could you help me kick off the next section?
OKです！
Sure thing!
ということで、ゲストパートに…
So then, on to the guest portion...
スタート！スタート！ Let's go!
Start! Start! Let's go!
単純で名高い独壇場じゃない
It's not a simple, famous exclusive stage
まだ早々妄想と偏見でFINE
It's fine with early delusions and prejudices for now
それ完全な完全な設定じゃない？
Isn't that a totally, completely fabricated setting?
これ買ってくれないか？
Won't you buy into this for me?
体型と内面と空間の不一致
A disconnect between build, personality, and vibe
この繊細さ敏感さ共有しよう
Let's share this delicacy and sensitivity
ほら冷静な表情は小さな超ハイ
Look, behind that calm face is a subtle high level of hype
見つけてくれないか？
Won't you spot it for me?
はいはいお姉さんしまっていこう
Alright, alright, big sister, let's pull it together
はいはい期待感背負っていこう
Alright, alright, let's shoulder all expectations
はいはいお姉さんしまっていこう
Alright, alright, big sister, let's pull it together
はいはい期待感背負っていこう
Alright, alright, let me carry everyone's expectations
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど 高嶺の花身 大人に扱っちゃイヤ
Holo-Holo-Hawk, Holo-Hawk, but an unattainable flower, don't treat me like an adult, I hate that
あのね 誰も彼も私と勘違い 驚きの愛
You know, everyone mistakes who I am, what surprising love
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど ポンコツみがチョイ あるだけで親近感
Holo-Holo-Hawk, Holo-Hawk, but just a bit of clumsiness gives a feeling of closeness
その才 その才 その才 受け止めてよね 高嶺の未来 乾杯
That talent, that talent, accept that talent, here's a toast to Takane's future!
しっかりウォッチ！
Keep a close watch!
合間言うな！
Don't interrupt!
辛いの苦手…
I'm bad with spicy food...
巻き縫いぬい！
Makin' Nui Nui!
え、ギャル系？
Huh, a gyaru type?
意外とギャップ系？
Surprisingly a gap-appeal type?
イメージ大変身！
A total image makeover!
オッケー！
Okay!
単純の感性で内臓じゃない
It's a simple sensibility, not visceral instincts
ああ心配ね 相談ね 散々ね でも
Ah, worrying, consulting, so much trouble, but still...
強制のいや朗々の配信じゃない
It's not a forced, cheerful stream
こちらって 限界態勢かい？
Are we at our absolute limit over here?
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど 捕食者の遺産 だから怖がっちゃイヤ
Holo-Holo-Hawk, Holo-Hawk, but with the legacy of a predator, so don't be scared of me
ほらね 爪も羽もおしゃれに研いで 隠しちゃいない
Look, my claws and wings are polished stylishly, nothing is hidden
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど 観察目がチョイ あるだけで緊張感
Holo-Holo-Hawk, Holo-Hawk, but just an observant eye adds a little tension
その才 その才 その才 受け止めてよね 高まる時代 乾杯
That talent, that talent, accept that talent, cheers to an escalating era!
はいはいお姉さんしまっていこう
Alright, alright, big sister, let me pull myself together
はいはい期待感背負っていこう
Alright, alright, let me carry everyone's expectations
はいはいお姉さんしまっていこう
Alright, alright, big sister, let's pull ourselves together
はいはい期待感背負っていこう
Alright, alright, let's shoulder all expectations!
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど 高嶺の花身 大人に扱っちゃイヤ
Holo-Holo-Hawk, Holo-Hawk, but an unattainable flower, don't treat me like an adult, I hate that
あのね 誰も彼も私と勘違い 驚きの愛
You know, everyone mistakes who I am, what surprising love
ホロホロホーク ホロホークだけど ポンコツみがチョイ あるだけで親近感
Holo-Holo-Hawk, Holo-Hawk, but just a bit of clumsiness gives a feeling of closeness
その才 その才 その才 受け止めてよね 高嶺の未来 乾杯
That talent, that talent, accept that talent, here's a toast to Takane's future!
会心！高まる時代 乾杯
Satisfying! Cheers to an escalating era!
オーバード
[Song: Overdose]
白くうつむく帰りの会で
At the homeroom meeting where everyone looks down quietly,
めんどくささを押し付けられてる
I'm being forced to deal with all the hassle.
何から何まで
From start to finish,
私語はやめて まとめ役なら
stop chatting; if you're the leader,
聴くを調節し 上手く調合してる
adjust how you listen and blend it together smoothly.
仲良しこよしで
Being all friendly-dovey...
だ・だ・だ・だ・黙れ黙りたまえよ
Sh-sh-sh-sh-shut up, shut your mouth!
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such strong words, can I?
シャットアウトしたい系 静かにしてほしいで
I'm the type who wants to shut everything out and have quiet...
ああ 私たち大望へ
Ah, toward our great ambition...
世界で て・て・て・て・吹く や・や・や
Blowing across the world, ya-ya-ya!
果たすその日まで
Until the day it comes to pass!
ね・ね・ね・ね・吹く や・や・や
N-n-n-n-blowing, ya-ya-ya!
あなたの周りも よ・よ・よ
Around you too, yo-yo-yo!
以来 て・て・て・て・吹く あ・れ・れ・あ
Ever since, t-t-t-t-blowing, a-re-re-a!
約束の地まで
To the promised land!
さあ高らかに バッテン バッテン
Come on, loud and clear, X, X!
て・て・て・て・吹く や・や・や
T-t-t-t-blowing, ya-ya-ya!
今日も期待 尊重の件だね
Today again, it's about respecting expectations, isn't it?
言い合いになるから 私一人でも
It'll turn into an argument, so even if I'm on my own...
やっていく気概さ
I've got the spirit to keep going.
すべて すべて すべて 任せて
Leave it all, leave it all, leave it all to me!
それをさせてよ
Let me handle that!
大事なことなの
It's an important matter.
分かっているでしょう
You understand, right?
白くうつむく帰りの会で
At the homeroom meeting where everyone looks down quietly,
めんどくさいまま
still feeling so troublesome...
今日も明日も過ぎていくのでしょう
I suppose today and tomorrow will just pass by.
花瓶に銘酒を捧げましょう
Let's offer fine sake in the vase.
時計の中 しおれたこと忘れてた
Inside the clock, I forgot that I had withered.
だ・だ・だ・だ・黙れ黙りたまえよ
Sh-sh-sh-sh-shut up, shut your mouth!
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
I can't say such strong words, can I?
シャットアウトしたい系 静かにしてほしいね
I'm the type who wants to shut everything out and have quiet...
ああ 私たち大望へ
Ah, toward our great ambition...
今が未来 見たかったはずなのに
Even though right now was supposed to be the future we wanted to see...
世界で て・て・て・て・吹く や・や・や
Blowing across the world, ya-ya-ya!
見ゆるその日まで
Until the day it becomes visible!
と・と・と・と・や・や・や
T-t-t-t, ya-ya-ya!
鼓舞の理 よ・よ・よ
The logic of encouragement, yo-yo-yo!
いざ て・て・て・て・吹く さ・さ・さ
Now, t-t-t-t-blowing, sa-sa-sa!
あなたの街中
In the middle of your town!
幽かに膨るは抜拳さ
Faintly swelling is the drawing of the blade!
て・て・て・て・吹く や・や・や
T-t-t-t-blowing, ya-ya-ya!
果たすその日まで
Until the day it comes to pass!
ね・ね・ね・ね・吹く や・や・や
N-n-n-n-blowing, ya-ya-ya!
あなたの周りも よ・よ・よ
Around you too, yo-yo-yo!
以来 て・て・て・て・吹く あ・れ・れ・あ
Ever since, t-t-t-t-blowing, a-re-re-a!
約束の地まで
To the promised land!
さあ高らかに バッテン バッテン
Come on, loud and clear, X, X!
て・て・て・て・吹く 知ったら
T-t-t-t-blowing, once you know it...
ヴィンテージワインを開けましょう
Let me pop open a vintage wine!
FIRST CRY
[Song: FIRST CRY]
誰かに笑われなくたって
Even if nobody laughs at it,
私のほうが
I myself...
もっと嫌いだ
hate it even more.
うるさいな 想像が視界を塞いで
Shut up already... imagination blocks my view,
いじめな理由を書き連ねる 虚実的にずっと居残り
endlessly lingering in falsehoods, listing reasons for being cruel.
窓の向こうに黒い影があって
There was a dark shadow beyond the window,
何も言わずにこっちを見ていた
looking this way without saying a word.
私はあなたに救われたくてのじゃない
It's not that I wanted to be saved by you.
産声は止められないもの
A newborn's first cry is something that cannot be stopped.
何千回とも一度 死に損なおう
Whether it's thousands of times or just once that I failed to die,
希望と絶望 夜中を纏って
clothed in hope and despair through the dead of night,
醜い光を許したいのは
the one who wants to forgive this ugly light...
他でもない私だった
was none other than myself.
息をして
Breathed...
目を開けて
Opened my eyes...
色が最後かどうか
Whether this is the end or not,
知るすべはないよ
there's no way to know,
知りたくもないよ
and I don't even want to know.
優しいな
So kind...
ほんとの闇は寄り添って
Real darkness cuddles close,
解けない答えを塗り潰した どうせ真っ白くもないよと
Painting over unsolvable answers, as if saying it wasn't pure white anyway.
窓をかすかに越えて
Lightly crossing through the window,
それは祈るような啜り泣きだった
it was a sobbing sound that felt like a prayer.
私はあなたを救える言葉を知らないけど
I don't know the words that could save you, but...
寂しいねって声をかけた
I called out, saying, "It feels lonely, doesn't it?"
何千回ともう一度死に損なおう
Let's fail to die thousands of times yet again.
希望と絶望のない夜中を跨がって
Straddling the midnight void of hope and despair.
何千回ともう一度生き永らえ
Let's survive thousands of times yet again.
私も続くよ 窓の向こう側へ
I will follow too, towards the other side of the window.
醜い光を来世たとき
When praising that ugly light,
終わらせられなかったループを
this loop that couldn't be ended...
歌にしよう
Let's turn it into a song.
Let me turn it into a song.
立派なこの羽に 泥をすりつけて貼っていた
Smearing and sticking mud onto these magnificent wings,
情けない姿で
in such a pathetic state.
信じられるものは 自分だけだと
Telling myself that the only thing I can trust is myself,
追い込んで 進み続けた
I pushed onward and kept advancing.
「あの子みたいにすれば？ 君じゃそれは無理だ」
"Why not be like her? You can't do that."
言わせておけばいいさ
Just let them say whatever they want.
だって一人 逆境の先 あいつらから遠ざかる
Because alone, beyond adversity, I move far away from them.
私の邪魔 させやしない
I won't let anyone stand in my way!
歪んだ鏡 見つめた眼
Eyes staring into a distorted mirror,
空へと飛んでいく私を見ないなんて バカっぽい
Not watching me fly towards the sky is just stupid.
失敗は止まったとき 今日も意地をはっているのに
Failure is when you stop; even though I'm being stubborn again today,
身の程 知らないものはないと
saying there's no one who doesn't know their place.
信じられるものを 見つけだすまで
Until I find something I can believe in,
どんなにだって 笑い飛ばして
no matter what, I'll laugh it off.
「あの子はもう終わりだ これ以上はないね」
"She's finished, she can't go any further."
言わせておけばいいさ
Just let them say whatever they want.
いつの日かで手を納めても 夢見てた体感せ
Even if I call it a day somewhere along the way, I'll experience what I dreamed of.
私はここで死にたくない
I don't want to die here!
一生の旅 逆境の先 あいつらから遠ざかる
A lifelong journey, beyond adversity, moving far away from them.
私の邪魔 させやしない
I won't let anyone stand in my way!
歪んだ鏡 見つめた眼
Eyes staring into a distorted mirror,
空へと飛んでいく私を見ないなんて バカっぽい
Not watching me fly towards the sky is just stupid.
バカっぽい
So stupid...
はい！ということで、3曲ゲストパートをお届けして
Alright! So with that, we've brought you three songs in the guest section,
先ほど『CHARISMA』という、jon-YAKITORYさんから書き下ろしていただいた楽曲を歌わせていただきました！いかがだったでしょうか！
and I just sang "CHARISMA," a song written for me by jon-YAKITORY! How did you like it?
イェーイ！イェーイ！ということで
Yay! Yay! So...
ちょっとね、喉も回復したので、歌えてよかったなと思いますけれど
My throat has recovered a bit, so I'm glad I was able to sing...
あ、トレンドが1位になったそうで、みんなありがとう！
Ah, it seems we reached #1 on trending! Thank you everyone!
たくさん呟いてくれて...あ、ポストしてくれてたね！
For posting so much... Ah, posting!
ポストしてくれてありがとう！まだまだたくさんポストしてくれると嬉しいです
Thank you for posting! I'd be happy if you keep posting more!
ハッシュタグ #鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドLIVE です！みんなありがとうー！
The hashtag is #鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドLIVE! Thank you everyone!
いや、今回はね、もうすでにリリースされている楽曲に関しては
Well, this time, regarding the songs that have already been released...
カリ先輩と、そしてマリン先輩、おかゆ先輩、そしてトワ様と一緒に歌わせていただいたんですけれど
I sang together with Calli-senpai, Marine-senpai, Okayu-senpai, and Towa-sama,
全く違った感じになってて、私楽しかったなと思うんですけれど
and it had a completely different vibe, which was so much fun for me,
皆様いかがだったでしょうか？
how was it for all of you?
いかがだったかな？
Did you enjoy it?
おめでと、おめでと、ありがとう！みんなありがとう！楽しかったかな？
"Congratulations", "Congratulations", thank you, thank you everyone! Did you enjoy it?
あ、「HOLO HAWKがめちゃくちゃ良かった」HOLO HAWKって言ってる海外ニキおりますね。ありがとう！
Ah, "HOLO HAWK was super good!" There are overseas fans saying HOLO HAWK. Thank you!
はい、なんかコメントがすごい勢いで流れているので固まってしまいました。
Yes, the comments were flowing so fast that I froze up!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ということで、これからね、2曲歌わせていただくんですけれども
So, I'm going to sing two songs now,
2曲で、あの...本編は終了（笑）
and after two songs... the main program ends!
いや嘘です！2曲以降もあるんですけれども、一応2曲ね、これから続けて歌わせていただきます。
No, I'm kidding! There are more after two songs, but for now I'll sing two songs back-to-back.
次に歌う曲なんですけれども
As for the next song I'm going to sing...
FAKE TYPE.さんに書き下ろしていただいた楽曲をやらせていただきます。「ひみつのおしごと」という楽曲なんですけれども
I'll perform a song written for me by FAKE TYPE. It's called "Himitsu no Oshigoto",
めちゃくちゃかっこいい曲になっているので、ぜひ楽しんで聴いていただければなと思います。
and it's a super cool song, so I hope you enjoy listening to it.
その前にちょっと水を飲んでもいいですか？
Before that, may I drink some water?
「いいよー」ということで水を飲みます！
"Sure!" So I'll drink water!
よし！歌える！俺ならいける！いけるよね？
Alright! I can sing! I got this! I got this, right?
みんな、いけるよね？
Everyone, we got this, right?
ということで、これから歌わせていただく曲は
So, the song I'm about to sing...
FAKE TYPE.さんに書き下ろしていただいた...もうボロボロだ（笑）楽曲「ひみつのおしごと」です！ぜひ聴いてください！
is written by FAKE TYPE... Ah, I'm messing up my words. The song "Himitsu no Oshigoto"! Please listen to it!
引けない
Can't back down
なんて言えない
Can't say that
後に引けない
No turning back
むやみにひっ散らかさない FRIDAY
Don't blindly make a mess, FRIDAY
いつもと手前のハラハラ 火花散らしてば命のからがら
Thrills right in front as usual, sparks fly as we barely escape with our lives
まっさらーしー 戸惑うダァんしー しなった角のステップで交わしちゃうぜ
Brand new, confused boys, dodging with a sharp-angled step
触りの社会が眠る頃に かなりな輩がバックする頃に
When mainstream society falls asleep, when those sketchy fellows retreat
持ちつ持たれつ表裏一体は 首を突っ込んで
Give and take, two sides of the same coin, poking my nose in
平日は Shooby Dooby Do
Weekdays, Shooby Dooby Do
週末も Shooby Dooby Do
Weekends too, Shooby Dooby Do
時にきつくハードに 時に平和なバードに 今宵ひみつの文字通り
Sometimes harsh and hard, sometimes a peaceful bird, tonight, literally a secret
BANG BANG BANG 狙って BANG BANG BANG 外さない CLEAR
BANG BANG BANG, take aim, BANG BANG BANG, I don't miss, CLEAR
イイ線行ってんだってランエガ
You're on the right track, Run Egar
言い分に足り得る意地を見せ
Showing enough persistence to justify my claim
威勢良く迫って BANG BANG BANG 捕らわれず COVER
Pressing aggressively, BANG BANG BANG, uncaptured, COVER
日々こうやって気取ってさ出番
Daily posing like this, it's my turn
ああ、土俵に乗ったぞ
Ah, I've entered the ring!
TAKE OFF 決して逃がさない
TAKE OFF, I'll never let you escape
剥いた牙を抜くまで 決して怪我させない
Until I pull out those bared fangs, I won't let you get hurt
守るためのこの看板
This signboard to protect
糸はいらない 根回しおいで お見舞いするあとの祭りおいで 響く昼の願いお仕置きの愛
Don't need thread, come with preparation, come to the belated festival where I pay my visits, echoing daytime wishes, punishing love
誰も彼も シグマホウの愛
Everyone, anyone, love of Sigma law
年始から Shooby Dooby Do
From the start of the year, Shooby Dooby Do
年末も Shooby Dooby Do
To the end of the year, Shooby Dooby Do
お任せあれ HANDY 表だってド直球に 元いひみつの文字通り
Leave it to me, HANDY, upfront and straight down the middle, or rather, literally a secret
BANG BANG BANG 狙って BANG BANG BANG 外さない CLEAR
BANG BANG BANG, take aim, BANG BANG BANG, I don't miss, CLEAR
イイ線行ってんだってランエガ しばしばルイは友を呼ぶ
You're on the right track, Run Egar, birds of a feather flock together
威勢良く迫って BANG BANG BANG 捕らわれず COVER
Pressing aggressively, BANG BANG BANG, uncaptured, COVER
日々こうやって気取ってさ出番
Daily posing like this, it's my turn
爪を剥き出し
Baring my claws
一見 高貴な企業もどきと 侮るのなら
If you look down on us as seemingly noble fake corporate types,
立ち外れて容赦なく 手短くなってやば殺される
Out of line, without mercy, cut short, perilously dispatched
本気か増しか弱音なんてすぐ眠れ
Are you serious or better off, go to sleep with your complaints immediately
混じり気ないハートビート 揺らすこの世界
Pure heartbeat shaking this world
咲いて果てど泥にまみれて明日かね
Blooming to the end, covered in mud, tomorrow maybe?
裏の裏までいただきじゃん
Taking it all, down to the inside out
いつだったって目立ったら笑顔
Whenever I stood out, a smile was there.
今だに縫い目は今日も呼ぶ息を
Even now, the seams draw in a breath today,
寄せては
pulling closer...
さとられず Cover
Unnoticed, I cover it up.
意味通り気取って去っては
Acting cool just as intended before slipping away,
通りに乗っ立つ
standing tall on the street.
今日も秘密の Day out
Today is another secret day out.
ラストはこの曲です！
This is the last song!
皆さん聴いてください、魔眼ウインク！
Everyone, please listen: "Magan Wink"!
So here, to be late...
Do you remember me?
シャルムな目元 メイクアップ
Charming eyes, made up,
捉え捉え捕まった
caught and held fast,
ナイスな目元 真っ赤っ赤
nice eyes glowing bright red.
それはウインク ウインク
That's a wink, a wink!
逃げてもずっと捕まえ
Even if you run, holding you tight,
クレイジーな台風の目
in the crazy eye of the storm.
ウインク
Wink!
冗談目論見デカい 目に入れたって痛くないくらい
Big jokes and grand schemes, so close it doesn't even hurt to look,
口ばしに Miss revenge
Miss Revenge at the ready.
仇返しなら 得意にしてた
Getting payback was always my specialty.
怖がってんの？ あっそ
Are you scared? Oh, really?
それ見たことか
See, what did I tell you?
まだまだ
Not yet, not yet!
安全じゃないから
Because it's not safe,
健全じゃないから
because it's not wholesome.
それがどうしたんだ Party
What about it? It's a party!
誰？ 目には目を
Who's that? An eye for an eye!
ウィンク
Wink!
See la la la la, be secret la la, give me a wink
See la la la la, や真っ赤っ赤
See la la la la, turned bright red!
OH, I, I, I want youで バイバイ安泰
OH, I, I, I want you, bye-bye to peaceful safety!
目移り目移る My eye eye
Glances wavering, my eye eye.
いいよ 目をつぶる半分ね
It's fine, I'll close my eyes halfway,
魔眼ウインク
with a Magic Eye Wink.
ほらほら 瞬く間に
Look, look, in the blink of an eye,
I, I, I kill you, Wink
後ろ指 刺したいならお好きにどうぞ
If you want to point fingers behind my back, go right ahead.
どうせ 振り返らん処置の残滓
After all, these remnants of measures won't look back.
お待たせ 迅速迅速 おさらばお恨みっこ
Thanks for waiting, swift and quick, farewell to holding grudges!
霊光な直感 Remember
Bright spiritual intuition, remember.
I'm coming back, coming back, coming back
目じゃない 眼中にない
Out of sight, out of mind!
そうさ 善良じゃないだろ
That's right, it's not virtuous, is it?
裁量じゃないだろ
It's not up to discretion, is it?
それがどうしたんだ Party
What about it? It's a party!
誰？ 目には目を 歯には歯を
Who's that? An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth!
類は何を呼ぶ
What do birds of a feather flock together for?
刹那的羽ばたきを知るウィン
Knowing the fleeting flutter of wings, win!
目が離せない
I can't take my eyes off!
完璧なウィンク
A perfect wink!
See la la la la, be secret la la, give me a wink
See la la la la, や真っ赤っ赤
See la la la la, turned bright red!
OH, I, I, I want youで バイバイ安泰
OH, I, I, I want you, bye-bye to peaceful safety!
目移り目移る My eye eye
Glances wavering, my eye eye.
もう目が離せない Eye eye eye
Can't take my eyes off anymore, eye eye eye!
魔眼ウインク
Magic Eye Wink!
ほらほら 瞬く間に
Look, look, in the blink of an eye,
I, I, I, I kill you
Wink!
Wink...
重大発表
[Major Announcement]
Project "L"
鷹嶺ルイ 1st Album
Takane Lui 1st Album
Liberty 発売決定！
"Liberty" Release Confirmed!
6/12 0:00 デジタルリリース
Digital Release on 6/12 0:00
hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPにて CD予約開始
CD Pre-orders Open on hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP
はい！ということで
All right! So with that,
重大告知させていただきました！
I've made a major announcement!
重大告知はなんと、鷹嶺ルイ 1st Album『Liberty』がリリース決定です！
The big news is that Takane Lui's 1st album, "Liberty", is officially being released!
イエーイ！
Yay!
あ、みんなね、拍手してくれてますね。ありがとうございます。
Ah, everyone is clapping for me. Thank you so much.
えー、こちらね、鷹嶺ルイの1st Album『Liberty』、皆さん予想できていましたでしょうか？
Were you all able to guess that Takane Lui's 1st album would be "Liberty"?
今回はですね、あのHoloXの1曲はあったんですけれども、そのほかは全曲鷹嶺ルイのオリジナル曲でライブをさせていただきました。
This time, although there was one HoloX song, all the other songs in the live performance were Takane Lui's original tracks.
この楽曲が全部入った『Liberty』、21時からhololive production OFFICIAL SHOPで販売開始になります！
"Liberty", containing all these tracks, will be available on the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP at 21:00!
デジタルリリースはこのあと24時から各種音楽サイトで配信が開始されます！
The digital release will stream on various music sites starting tonight at midnight!
『魔眼ウインク』とね、今日お披露目した新曲を含む全10曲のオリジナルアルバムになっております。
It's an original album with 10 songs in total, including "Magan Wink" and the new track unveiled today.
収録内容は、こちら！
The tracklist is right here!
はい、こちらですね。
Yes, right here.
先ほどやらせていただいた『ひみつのおしごと』、『魔眼ウインク』に始まり...
Starting with "Himitsu no Oshigoto", which I performed earlier, and "Magan Wink"...
マリン先輩とやった『ばかばっか』、『FIRST CRY』、『CHARISMA』、『オーバーロード』、『Tori To Re:TreaT』...
"Baka Bakka" with Marine-senpai, "FIRST CRY", "CHARISMA", "OVERLOAD", "Tori To Re:TreaT"...
『ホロホーク』、そして「あれ？『夢ができたの』『TSUBASA』、あれ？まだやってないな」っていう曲もありますけれども、この10曲が入ったアルバムになっております。
"HoloHawk", and then "Wait, 'Yume ga Dekitano' and 'TSUBASA'? I haven't done those yet!" There are songs like that too, making up a 10-track album.
アルバムジャケットのイラストはSOLANI先生に描いていただき、ロゴはsaku39先生に作っていただきました！
The jacket illustration was drawn by SOLANI-sensei, and the logo design was created by saku39-sensei!
OFFICIAL SHOPでの購入特典として、MVから厳選したシーンのカットのフィルム風しおりをランダム封入させていただきます！
As a bonus for buying on the OFFICIAL SHOP, a film-style bookmark of selected MV scenes will be randomly included!
全4種類って書いてあるんですが、シークレットもあるので全5種類の中から1枚封入させていただきます。
It says 4 types, but with the secret one, 1 out of 5 types in total will be enclosed.
さらに！直筆サイン入りのアナザージャケットも付いてきちゃいます！こちら！
Furthermore! An alternate jacket with a handwritten signature is also included! Here!
いや、かっこいいですね、白黒で。
Wow, this monochrome look is so cool.
はい、こちら購入者全員に直筆サインで書いていただきますので...
Yes, I will personally sign this for every single purchaser...
私の腕が大丈夫かって心配あるかもしれませんが、全然書いちゃうんで！思いを込めて書いちゃうんでね！ぜひ購入していただけたら嬉しいなと思います。よろしくお願いします！
You might worry about my arm, but I'll write every single one with love! I'd be so happy if you bought it. Thank you!
注意事項なのですが、今回のアルバムの到着時期がですね、誕生日グッズよりも早めに発送できる予定になっておりますので、早くアルバムが欲しい方はカートを誕生日グッズと分けて注文をしてください。
One note: the album is scheduled to ship earlier than the birthday merch, so if you want it sooner, please order it in a separate cart from the birthday merch.
アルバムのカートと誕生日グッズのカートを一緒にしてしまいますと、誕生日グッズと一緒に届くので到着が遅くなってしまいますので注意してください。
If you combine the album and birthday merch in one cart, it will be delivered together with the birthday merch and arrive later, so please be careful!
そして配信冒頭でもお知らせしましたが、21時からは鷹嶺ルイ誕生日記念グッズ2024も発売開始されます！こちら！
And as mentioned earlier in the stream, Takane Lui Birthday Commemorative Goods 2024 go on sale at 21:00! Here it is!
はい！ビッグタオル、ランダム缶バッジ、おでかけルイーぬいぐるみ、ボディ痛バッグの4種類でフルセットもございます。フルセットには箔押し複製サイン入りチケット風特典カードと特典ボイスが付いてきます。
Yes! There's a full set of 4 items: Big Towel, Random Pin Badge, Odekake Lui Plushie, and Ita Body Bag. The full set comes with a ticket-style bonus card featuring a foil-stamped signature and bonus voice!
今回は数量限定版をご用意させていただいておりまして、数量限定版には特典カードに直筆メッセージを書いちゃいます！アルバムは直筆サイン、こちらは直筆メッセージになってますのでご注意ください。
We also have a limited quantity version available, where I'll write a handwritten message on the bonus card! Please note that the album has a handwritten signature, while this has a handwritten message.
まだまだあります！21時5分からは『魔眼ウインク』のミュージックビデオがプレミア公開します！イエーイ！
There's still more! At 21:05, the "Magan Wink" music video will premiere! Yay!
すごい楽しみに待っていた方もいるんじゃないでしょうか？今回もオーバーロード、ばかばっか、ホロホークに続いてYMさんに作っていただきましたMVになっておりますが、すごくかっこいい感じに仕上がっているのでぜひ見ていただければなと思います。
Many of you have probably been waiting for this! Following OVERLOAD, Baka Bakka, and HoloHawk, this MV was created by YM-san as well. It turned out super cool, so please check it out!
そんな『魔眼ウインク』をたくさんの人に聴いてもらうために、#魔眼ウインク投稿チャレンジ キャンペーンも開催中でございます！6月30日までなので要チェックです！
To share "Magan Wink" with as many people as possible, the #MaganWink Post Challenge campaign is currently underway! Check it out before June 30th!
そしてここからはコラボのお知らせです。ちょっとね、告知が多くなってすいません！コラボのお知らせです。なんと！DAMさんでコラボキャンペーンを実施することになりました！イエーイ！
And now for collaboration news. Sorry for having so many announcements! Here's the collab news: we are doing a collaboration campaign with DAM! Yay!
精密採点で
In the precision scoring campaign,
課題曲を歌いまして
singing the designated songs,
参加者全員の
when all participants'
累計得点が
cumulative score
10万点に達しますと
reaches 100,000 points,
限定メッセージ動画をプレゼントいたします！
a special message video will be gifted!
参加してくださった方には
Everyone who participates
オリジナル壁紙プレゼント！
will receive an original wallpaper!
さらに抽選で10名様に
Plus, 10 lucky winners chosen by lottery
オリジナルステンレスボトルをプレゼント！
will get an original stainless steel bottle!
なんか下、私見えてるな
Wait, I can see myself down there...
DAMでたくさんみんな歌ってくれると嬉しいです！
I'll be so happy if everyone sings a lot on DAM!
そんなDAMさんにて『オーバード』の
And on DAM, for "Overdrive,"
本人映像が本日
the official music video background
6月11日より順次配信開始しています！こちら！
is available starting today, June 11th! Right here!
ミュージックビデオと一緒に『オーバード』が歌えるので
You can sing "Overdrive" along with the MV,
この機会に足を運んでみてください！
so please go check it out during this opportunity!
今回のコラボを記念して
To commemorate this collaboration,
渋谷のグリコビジョンなど
in Shibuya, on the Glico Vision screen...
複数箇所でですね
and across multiple locations,
ビジョン放送が決定しました！
outdoor vision broadcasts have been confirmed!
すげー！
Awesome!
こちらね、7月頃から放映予定なので
Broadcasts are scheduled around July,
詳細はお待ちいただければなと思います！
so please stay tuned for more details!
また詳細発表させていただきます！
We'll announce the details soon!
まだまだ嬉しいお知らせがあります！
There are still more exciting announcements!
あと、あともうちょっとです！
Just a few more!
6月13日(木) 22時より放送の
On Thursday, June 13th from 10:00 PM,
ラジオ『SCHOOL OF LOCK!』に
on the radio show "SCHOOL OF LOCK!",
私、先生として初出演させていただきます！
I will make my first appearance as a guest teacher!
生徒の皆さん、ぜひぜひ聴いてください！
So all you students out there, please tune in!
嬉しいお知らせをたくさんさせていただきましたが
I've shared a lot of happy announcements,
ここでですね
and now...
今日のこのライブを一緒に作ってくれた
I'd like to introduce the wonderful band members
素敵なバンドメンバーの皆さんをご紹介させていただきます！
who helped make today's live stream possible!
バンドメンバーの皆さん、どうぞ！
Band members, please come on out!
お待たせしました！長くてすみませんね
Sorry to keep you waiting! Sorry that took long!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
イェーイ！戻ってきてくれました！
Yay! They're back!
ということで、ちょっと紹介をしていきましょうかね
So then, let's introduce everyone.
準備は大丈夫ですか、皆さん？
Is everyone ready?
皆さん大丈夫ですね
Looks like everyone's ready.
うんうんって頷いてる
They're nodding along!
ということで、バンドメンバーの紹介です！
And so, here are our band members!
それでは...
First up...
ベース、Kさん！
Bass, Kei-san!
ふー！かっこいい！かっこいいね、やっぱりベースって
Woo! So cool! Bass sounds so cool!
低音でかっこいいよね。ありがとうございます！
Those deep tones are awesome. Thank you!
そして、キーボード
And next, on keyboard...
くわっちさん！
Kuacchi-san!
ふー！おしゃれですね！
Woo! How stylish!
やんちゃ、やんちゃですね。ありがとうございます！
A bit playful there! Thank you!
そして、ギター
And next, on guitar...
カルロスさん！
Karurossu-san!
ふー！かっこいい！ありがとうございます！
Woo! So cool! Thank you very much!
いやーかっこいいな！
Man, that was so cool!
はい、そして最後にバンドマスターで
And finally, our band master...
ドラムでバンドマスターもしてくださった、ぐーさん！
On drums and acting as band master, Gu-san!
ふー！いやーかっこいいですね！ありがとうございます！
Woo! So cool! Thank you!
そしてですね、このメンバーには
And also, while they aren't here...
3Dでは登場していないんですけれども
in 3D like the rest of the members,
裏にですね、マニピュレーターの
behind the scenes, our manipulator...
パスタさんがいます！ありがとうございます！
Pasta-san is here! Thank you!
私がじゃあ効果音を... あ、手を振ってくれてますね！
Let me make a sound effect... Oh, they're waving!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
というメンバーでお送りさせていただきました！
We presented today's stream with this team!
ということで、あとね2曲歌わせていただくんですけれども
Now, we still have two more songs to perform,
21時15分からは
and starting at 21:15,
メンバーシップ限定ライブも生バンドでお届けしたいと思います！
our members-only live will also feature a live band!
この機会にぜひメンバーシップに参加してみてください！
Please take this opportunity to join our membership!
ということで、まだやっていない2曲がありますね
So then, we still have two songs left.
次の曲はですね
The next song is...
『夢ができたの』という曲になるんですけれども
a song titled "Yume ga Dekita no"...
これは、私があの
And this is a song...
ホロライブに入る前
from before I joined hololive,
ホロライブを見つけて、「ホロライブに入りたいな」って
when I found hololive and thought, "I want to join hololive."
思った...
I asked...
その思いのままを書き下ろしていただいた楽曲になります
for a song written capturing those exact feelings.
聴いていただきたいんですが、その前に...
I'd love for you to listen to it, but before that...
水を飲みます！
I'm gonna drink some water!
ちょっとすみません、水を飲ませてください
Sorry, let me drink some water.
ね、このままいったらエモいやんって思ったでしょ？
You thought it was gonna be emotional right away, right?
水を飲まないとやっていけなかったんで
I couldn't keep going without water!
ということで、皆さん準備は大丈夫ですかね？
So then, is everyone ready?
ということで、ちょっと...
So...
ホロライブに入って、私のたくさんの夢が叶っていたんですけれども
After joining hololive, so many of my dreams came true,
やっぱりホロライブを目指したきっかけという思いは忘れたくないなと思いまして
but I never want to forget what made me strive for hololive.
この曲を歌わせていただきます
With that in mind, I will now perform this song.
聴いてください
Please listen.
夢ができたの
I've found a dream.
そこは変わった世界 憧れた
I longed for that strange, changed world,
星たちの世界
a world of stars.
両手いっぱいの愛 持ち寄って
Bringing hands full of love together,
明かりにしている
we turn it into light.
間違いことだけ 占めるような街
In a town filled only with mistakes,
夢ができたの この星の夜は 暗いでしょう
I've found a dream. The night on this planet must be dark.
どんなときでも とびきり優しい 灯火になりたいの
No matter when, I want to become an exceptionally gentle light.
夕暮れに口を尖らせて泣いた 昨日の私は
Pouting and crying at sunset, the me of yesterday
ネガティブ丸めて捨てた 生まれ変わったの
balled up all the negativity, threw it away, and was reborn.
高い壁が立つなら 当たって砕けちゃえ
If a high wall stands in front of me, I'll just smash right through it!
一人きりでは この星の夜は 暗いでしょう
All alone, the night on this planet must be dark.
君の明日を 照らし出すような 灯火になりたいの
I want to become a light that illuminates your tomorrow.
夢ができたの この星の夜は 暗いでしょう
I've found a dream. The night on this planet must be dark.
どんなときでも とびきり優しい 灯火になりたいの
No matter when, I want to become an exceptionally gentle light.
はいということで、『夢ができたの』歌わせていただきました。
So, that was my performance of "Yume ga Dekita no".
またね、アルバムの詳細だったりとか、楽曲のこだわりについては振り返り配信とかでね、お話しさせていただければなと思います。
I'll share more about the album details and my thoughts on the songs during a recap stream later.
そして、次が本当に最後の曲になります。今日は本当に皆さん集まってくれて、応援してくれてありがとうございました。
And next will really be the last song. Thank you all so much for coming today and supporting me!
ちょっとね、喉が不完全ではあるので...
My throat isn't in top shape today...
またね、なんかリベンジしたいな～なんて...
so I'd love to do a revenge performance sometime...
リベンジさせていただきたいなと思っております。
I really hope to get a chance to make it up to you!
はい、すごい生バンドライブ、初の私の試みになったんですが、すごく楽しかったです。
This live band concert was a first-time attempt for me, but it was so much fun!
こうやってね、夢を叶えていけるのは、ルイ友さんをはじめ、こうやってホロライブを盛り上げてくださるホロリスの皆さん、そしてホロライブのメンバー、そして運営さんのおかげだと思っているので、本当に皆さんありがとうございます。
Being able to fulfill my dreams like this is thanks to my Luitomo, all the fans hyping up Hololive, the members, and staff. Thank you so much!
これからも鷹嶺ルイ、頑張っていきたいと思いますので、皆さん応援ぜひぜひよろしくお願いします！
Takane Lui will keep giving it her all, so please continue to support me!
夢はソロライブ！頑張って叶えるぞー！
My dream is a solo live concert! I'll work hard to make it come true!
ということで、ちょっとお水を飲んで...
So, let me grab a quick drink of water...
歌わせていただきます。
and then I'll perform.
最後の曲は、私が作詞に参加させていただきました。
For this final song, I participated in writing the lyrics.
ルイ友さんへの感謝の気持ちも込めて歌いたいと思います。聴いてください。『TSUBASA』。
I'll sing it filled with gratitude for all the Luitomo. Please listen to "TSUBASA".
泣かないで 私がいつもついてるよ
Don't cry, I'm always here for you.
つらさを隠しがちな君 庇ってあげたいよ
You always tend to hide your pain, I want to protect you.
大丈夫 泣かないで でも無理に笑わないで
It's okay, don't cry, but don't force a smile either.
ゆっくり空を見上げてごらん 似たもの同士
Take it slow and look up at the sky, we're two of a kind.
翼を痛めた君 今度は私が支えるから
You whose wings were hurt, this time I'll support you.
ピカピカな夢に 泣き出した日もあったけれど
There were days we cried over dazzling dreams, but...
君の言う「大丈夫」で 諦めずに来られた
Your reassuring words kept me from giving up.
まだ遅くないよ ここから始まるストーリー
It's not too late, our story starts right here.
さあ 少し休んで 涙を拭いて歩き出そう
Come on, rest a bit, wipe your tears, and let's start walking.
覚えてる 私もね 折れかけた翼抱いて
I remember too, holding onto my broken wings...
励ます君に甘えてた あの日のこと
...leaning on you as you cheered me on back on that day.
雨上がりの切なさに 私たちは強く生まれ変わる
Through the sadness after the rain, we are reborn stronger.
心ない声に 耳を塞ぐ日もあるけれど
Though there are days we block out heartless voices...
味方がここにいるって 逢えてよかったよ
...I'm so glad we met and that I have an ally right here.
まだあふれていくよ これから叶えるストーリー
It keeps overflowing, the story we'll fulfill from now on.
さあ 手を取り合って 遥かな未来を見つめよう
Come, let's take each other's hands and gaze into the distant future.
これから先は 傷つかずに進めない
From here on out, we can't move forward without getting hurt.
だけど覚えてて 君はもう一人じゃないから 胸を張って
But remember, you are not alone anymore, so hold your head high!
私たちは今も 不器用で無邪気な言葉 譲れない夢抱いて 翼羽ばたかせよう
Even now, holding onto clumsy, innocent words and unyielding dreams, let's spread our wings!
大空へ！
Into the vast sky!
今日は来てくれて本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming today!
向かい風受けて 高く高く飛んでいこう
Facing the headwind, let's fly higher and higher.
また雨が降り出しても 私が守るから
Even if it starts to rain again, I'll protect you.
この先にどんな未来が待っているか分からない
I don't know what kind of future awaits us up ahead...
だけど信じている 君とならどこまでも行ける
...but I believe that with you, I can go anywhere!
一緒に見る夢のストーリー
This story of the dream we see together.
今日はみんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for coming today!
すごい楽しい誕生日になりました！
This has been such a fun birthday!
アルバムもグッズもよろしくね！
Please support the album and merch too!
ソロライブの夢、叶えよう！
Let's make our dream of a solo live come true!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!